{
    "subject": "resource/Dolores_Guinness",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1936-07-31",
    "human_readable": "Dolores Guinness was born on July 31, 1936.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9799612164497375,
            "question": "What is Dolores Guinness's age if she was born on July 31, 1936?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8562988042831421,
            "question": "When was Dolores Guinness born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6689158082008362,
            "question": "What is Dolores Guinness's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.598243772983551,
            "question": "Is Dolores Guinness's birthday before or after summer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5862449407577515,
            "question": "Dolores Guinness's birthdate falls in what season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5861833095550537,
            "question": "If Dolores Guinness was born on a Friday, what day of the week would be her birthday this year?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4888209402561188,
            "question": "In what year did Dolores Guinness come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3322696387767792,
            "question": "If today is October 26, 2023, how old would Dolores Guinness be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17203053832054138,
            "question": "July 31st falls in which month?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.11050821840763092,
            "question": "What month follows July?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Dolores Guinness was born on July 31, 1936.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5539_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=July 31st falls in which month?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5539_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today is October 26, 2023, how old would Dolores Guinness be?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5539_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Dolores Guinness come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5539_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5539_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can confirm that:\n\n* The birth date of Dolores Guinness is indeed July 31, 1936.\n\nGiven this information, the answer to the query is:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents explicitly state that \"Dolores Guinness was born on July 31, 1936, in Charlottenburg, Berlin, Germany.\" Therefore, the information provided is correct."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}